# HAEUN SONG

(647) 473-5160 | haeunsong0615@gmail.com | LinkedIn: haeun--song | GitHub: @haeunyy96

### **PROFILE**

I am a software developer with a background in pediatric nursing and anatomy education. With previous experiences in working in a fast-paced environment, where multi-tasking, prioritization and teamwork skills are crucial, I am now very passionate to build a useful, engaging, and accessible websites and applications.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5 | CSS3 | SCSS | JavaScript (ES6, ES5) | Version Control (Git) | React | JQuery | RESTful API | Firebase Node.js | Responsive Designs | Performance Testing | Project Scope Management | Team-based development Pair programming | Teamwork | Leadership | Communication | Facilitation skills | Prioritization

## **EDUCATION**

## Juno College of Technology

• Web Development Bootcamp

# **University of Toronto**

- Honours Bachelor of Science, Nursing (BScN)
- Honours Bachelor of Science (BSc); Major Human Biology and Physiology
- Certificate in Project Management

# **PROJECTS**

Trivia Time <u>View Live | View Code</u>

- An interactive game app that allows users to play against each other or by themselves and test their knowledge on random facts.
- Incorporated HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, RESTful API, Firebase and React.js

Recipe Today <u>View Live | View Code</u>

- A responsive and interactive website created using API to allow user input of ingredients of their choice and show recipes in return.
- Incorporated HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, RESTful API and React.is

Scene It <u>View Live | View Code</u>

- An interactive website using RESTful API to search for things to do at different travel destinations.
- Incorporated HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, and RESTful API

Bar One <u>View Live</u> | <u>View Code</u>

- A multipage-responsive website for promotion of a potential business that will enable the business to have a better user-interaction and navigation
- Incorporated HTML5, CSS3, SASS and JavaScript

# PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

## University of Toronto | Web Developer | Contract

Jan 2023 - Current

Division of Anatomy, Department of Surgery, Faculty of Medicine

• Designing and developing an interactive website with authentication for 3D Anatomy viewer used by 400+ students.

# University of Toronto | Gross Anatomy Lab Demonstrator and Prosector

May 2018 - Current

Division of Anatomy, Department of Surgery, Faculty of Medicine | Faculty of Dentistry

- Supervised full-body cadaveric dissections for professional students with no previous dissection experiences
- Instructed comprehensive anatomy lab sessions for medical, dental and physiotherapy students
- Created 500+ dissections and plastination of cadavers for use with various anatomy courses at the university

# The Hospital for Sick Children (SickKids) | Registered Nurse

Aug 2020 - Aug 2021

8C: Burns, Plastic Surgery, Urology and Ophthalmology Unit

- Provided client experience through care plan creation with several stake holders (doctors, pharmacists, and social workers) tailored individually for each patient.
- Supported 500+ patients' hospitalization journey from pre-admission to discharge by providing compassionate care for patients and families and incorporating understanding of different social determinants of health